seosoftwareservices.com 2015-03-25

# SSS Technology Privacy Policy

**SEO Software Services Privacy Policy** is solely based on using the valuable information collected from the website in a customized form which is integrated to provide maximum benefit to our users. The information thus gathered is stored in a much secured way on our domain servers. We, SEO Software Services are the sole custodians of this information, and we do not disseminate, sell or rent it unless it is mandatory as per the law and do not involve any legal complications, thereof. It may also be used to apprise you with latest information on trends, developments, special events pertaining to our segment, and offers best suited for you, based on your existing business model. 

Simultaneously, we also protect your sensitive information in all possible ways. Only, in cases of specific job requirements, we do grant access to this data, at the same time adhering to stringent policy measures to prevent utter violation of such information by the users. We may also use this information to identify and sue the perpetrators infringing upon our privacy policy (either intentionally or unintentionally). 

We may use the data we have to make you familiar with products and services that might be of interest to you. We might also provide you with relevant information from third parties to you which are significant to your requirements. 

Because the Internet Protocol is universally accessible, the information you provide us may be disseminated to third parties that do not adhere to data protection guidelines 

Our success relies on our expertise to provide you information that our customers really need to utilize to their optimum benefit. We may from time to time analyze the data we have to find out what is most likely to appeal to individual customers and web-site users. We also provide aggregate statistics about our customers, their sales statistics, operating system, browser type, demographics, Internet domain, and profile, traffic patterns, and other site information to third parties which we think are reliable and reputed, but these statistics do not include personal information which may disclose individual identity. We do hope that this will provide you with lots of fun and experience while browsing. We or our partners and co-partners having a tie-up with us may occasionally contact you by email or telecon to brief you more about our products and services or to take your feedback and valuable opinion on our product range and services offered by us. 

We deploy stringent hiring process to weed-out employees having a shoddy background. As an employer, the incumbents we hire are asked to sign a confidentiality agreement that refrains them from disclosing any significant information to which they have instant access, to individuals or entities, even that have close proximity to them. In the case of any employee leaving the company or being compelled to quit due to unavoidable circumstances, we take no chances and switch the access codes that the employee had been using to access the customers accounts. 

It is our sole discretion to amend this privacy policy at any point of time. However, if any changes are being enforced, we will display the alterations on our web site and on the home page to make you aware that a new privacy policy has been implemented. We may also contact you personally to brief you about the new changes incorporated by us.
